Guide to the Creative Time Records MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibitions and Projects, 1974-2012; 204.08 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 75 manuscript boxes, 275 jewel cases, 22 box binders, 8 oversized flat boxes, 9 oversized folders, 5 shared record cartons, 2 tall manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 shared flat box, and 1 shared casset
  - Projects at the Chamber by Multiple Artists -- Chamber of Commerce, November-December 1982
    - Correspondence and Programs (Box 142, Folder 14, Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 18, Folder 6-7)
  - Press -- General, 1982 (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Artists' Works or Proposals for Unknown or Unrealized Exhibitions, 1982-2001
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- John Pietro Compilation Tape (Box 144, Cd 179.0042)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tony Fisher and Steven Ausbury -- "The Lost Opera" (Box 149, Dvd 179.0463)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Peter Freusen -- "Descartes" (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0774)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Kit-Yin Snyder -- Enrico IV Installation, September 1990 (Box 149, Dvd 179.0435)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Kit-Yin Snyder -- Enrico IV Installation (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0434)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tony Fisher and Steven Ausbury -- "The Lost Opera" (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0462)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Noam Toran -- "Object for Lonely Men" (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0558)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Life During Wartime" (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0686)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tannis Hugill -- "Hanging Woman" and "Flagella: A Space Probe" (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0687)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Joan Giummo -- "Fire Sign" (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0688)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Marianne Goldberg -- Excerpts of "Environs" (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0689)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- John Pietro Compilation Tape (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0041)
  - Art in the Anchorage 1 by Multiple Artists, May-October 1983
    - Electronic Records, cuid40862
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 142, Folder 17-18, Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 18, Folder 8-10)
    - Slides (Box 112, Folder Sleeves 20-24)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Drunken Madness (Box 146, Dvd 179.0242)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Drunken Madness (Box 151, Dvd 179.0693)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Drunken Madness (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0241)
  - Art on the Beach 5: Six Collaborative Projects by Multiple Artists -- Battery Park City Landfill, July-September 1983
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 143, Folder 1, Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 18, Folder 11-12, Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 112, Folder Sleeves 14-19)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Live at 5 (Box 149, Dvd 179.0477)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Live at 5 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0476)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Magnificent Force, Panache, Sesame St." (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0690)
  - Art on the Beach, 1983-1985 Retrospective Program and General Press, 1986 (Box 143, Folder 2, Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Press -- General, 1983 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Photographs from Unidentified Exhibitions, 1983-1984 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Walk-In Theater for Pedestrians by Carmella Saraceno, January-April 1984
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 50, Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
    - Slides (Box 112, Folder Sleeve 25)
  - Art on the Beach 6 by Multiple Artists -- Battery Park City Landfill, July-September 1984
    - Electronic Records, cuid40863
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 51, Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 19, Folder 4-5, Box 22, Folder 289)
    - Slides (Box 112, Folder Sleeves 26-34)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- MTV (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0747)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tape 1 (Box 147, Dvd 179.0330)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tape 2 -- Kay Lynn (Box 147, Dvd 179.0344)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Kay Lynn 2 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0729)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tape 3 -- Kay Lynn (Box 148, Dvd 179.0356)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Kay Lynn 3 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0732)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tape 5 (Box 148, Dvd 179.0376)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Highlight Reel (Box 147, Dvd 179.0316)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Highlights -- Edited by Dan Freel (Box 148, Dvd 179.0413)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Highlights (Box 151, Dvd 179.0705)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Highlight Reel (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0315)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tape 1 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0329)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tape 2 -- Kay Lynn (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0343)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tape 3 -- Kay Lynn (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0355)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- MTV (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0651)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tape 5 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0375)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Highlights -- Edited by Dan Freel (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0412)
  - Touch Sanitation Show by Mierle Laderman Ukeles, September-October 1984
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 52, Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
    - Slides (Box 113, Folder Sleeves 1-2)
  - Nighttrippers by Kaylynn Sullivan with Henry Threadgill -- Programs and Press, December 1984 (Box 2, Folder 53, Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Press -- General, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Art in the Anchorage 2 by Multiple Artists, May-June 1985
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 58-59, Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 104, Folder 1-3)
    - Slides (Box 114, Folder Sleeves 1-14)
  - Art on the Beach 7 by Multiple Artists -- Battery Park City Landfill, July-September 1985
    - Electronic Records, cuid40864
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 60-63, Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 104, Folder 4-6, Box 22, Folder 290-291)
    - Slides (Box 113, Folder Sleeves 19-34)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Last Day Concert, Part 1 (Box 145, Cd 179.0120)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Last Day Concert, Part 2 (Box 145, Cd 179.0121)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy (Box 144, Cd 179.0075)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- NPR (Box 145, Cd 179.0108)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Yoshiko Chuma, Lenny Pickett, Fred Wilson (Box 147, Dvd 179.0322)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dieter Froese -- "Chuma Dicket Wilson" (Box 151, Dvd 179.0714)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy-- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Tape 2 (Box 147, Dvd 179.0332)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy-- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Tape 3 (Box 147, Dvd 179.0320)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy-- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Tape 7 (Box 147, Dvd 179.0318)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Yoshiko Chuma (Box 147, Dvd 179.0314)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CBC Master #1 (Box 147, Dvd 179.0326)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CBC Master #2 (Box 147, Dvd 179.0328)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CBC Camera Master #1 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0720)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CBC Camera Master #2 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0723)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Yoshiko Chuma, Lenny Pickett, Fred Wilson (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0321)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Tape 2 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0331)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Tape 3 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0331)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Tape 7 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0317)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "School of Hard Knocks" -- Yoshiko Chuma (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0313)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- CBC Master #1 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0325)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- CBC Master #2 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0327)
    - Audio Recording -- Original (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0074)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- NPR (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0107)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Last Day Concert (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0119)
  - A Drop in the Bucket by Jane Greengold, September-November 1985
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 64, Box 21, Folder 260, Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Prints (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 114, Folder Sleeves 15-17)
  - Stroll Magazine, Vol. 1, No. 1, Spring-Summer 1985 (Box 21, Folder 259)
  - Subway Art, 1985
    - Electronic Records -- Videos, 1985; cuid40871
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 2 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0750)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 3 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0753)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 4 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0756)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 5 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0759)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 7 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0762)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 8 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0765)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 9 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0768)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Live from Underground" 10 (Box Shared Fales 146, Dvd 179.0771)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 2 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0652)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 3 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0653)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 4 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0654)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 5 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0655)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 7 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0656)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 8 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0657)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 9 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0658)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 10 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0659)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Live from Underground" 11 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0660)
  - Press -- General, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Holiday Greeting Card by Calvin Reid, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - B. Holden to Diderot by Barry Holden, March-June 1986
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 2, Folder 69-70, Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 104, Folder 8-9)
    - Slides (Box 115, Folder Sleeves 1-5)
  - Art in the Anchorage 3: The Memory Theatre of Giulio Camillo by Multiple Artists, June-July 1986
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 71-72, Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 104, Folder 10, Box 105, Folder 1-3, Box 22, Folder 292)
    - Slides (Box 114, Folder Sleeves 22-28)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0204)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0203)
  - Performance in the Park 1 by Multiple Artists, August-September 1986
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 2, Folder 73, Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, Transparencies, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 105, Folder 4-6)
    - Slides (Box 115, Folder Sleeves 6-26)
  - Stroll Magazine, Vol. 2, No. 1-2, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 261-262, Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Press -- General, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Holiday Greeting Card by David Humphrey, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 76, Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Art in the Anchorage 4 by Multiple Artists, June-July 1987
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 79, Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 22, Folder 293, Box 138, Folder 1-5)
    - Slides (Box 116, Folder Sleeves 16-22)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Guerrilla Girls (Box 145, Cd 179.0086)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- John Kelly (Box 150, Dvd 179.0501)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Guerrilla Girls (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0085)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- John Kelly (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0500)
  - Performance in the Park 2 by Multiple Artists, June-September 1987
    - Correspondence, Programs, Proposals, and Press (Box 2, Folder 80, Box 21, Folder 264, Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 106, Folder 1-5)
    - Slides (Box 116, Folder Sleeves 1-15)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Lenny Pickett with the Borneo Horns (Box 144, Cd 179.0044)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Clarice Marshall (Box 147, Dvd 179.0290)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Lenny Pickett with the Borneo Horns (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0043)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Clarice Marshall (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0289)
  - Art on the Beach 8 by Multiple Artists -- Hunter's Point, Queens, July-October 1987
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 81-83, Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Blueprints (Flat-file-folder 5, Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 138, Folder 6-9)
    - Slides (Box 116, Folder Sleeves 23-29)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Mark Antrobus -- "Mud People" (Box 146, Dvd 179.0254)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Mark Antrobus -- "Mud People" (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0253)
  - Press -- General, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Battery Maritime Building South Ferry Center for the Arts Project with Dance Theater Workshop, Inc., 1987-1991
    - Proposals and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 96-100, Box 36, Folder 6, Box 21, Folder 265)
    - Blueprints (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Prints (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - In the WINTER GARDEN: Relay by Connie Beckley and Anggrek by Alice Farley and Company, May 1988
    - Electronic Records, cuid40865
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 86, Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 139, Folder 1-4)
    - Slides (Box 118, Folder Sleeve 26)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Alice Farley -- The Water Garden -- Cooper-Hewitt Museum, August 1982 (Box 146, Dvd 179.0238)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Alice Farley -- The Water Garden (Box 151, Dvd 179.0687)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Alice Farley -- The Water Garden -- Cooper-Hewitt Museum, August 1982 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0237)
  - Misfortunes of Desire Acted Out at an Imaginary Location Symbolizing Everything Worth Having by Survival Research Laboratories (SRL), May 1988
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 2, Folder 87, Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Poster (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Prints (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Shea Stadium and CBS News (Box 149, Dvd 179.0465)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 150, Dvd 179.0553)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 151, Dvd 179.0603)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- TV Spots, 1981, 1983, 1986, and 1989 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0557)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- CNN -- Stanford Conference on Design, July-August 1987 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0597)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "The Virtues of Negative Fascination", 1985-1986 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0599)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Mark Pauline -- 1989 Sculpture Grant Award Exhibition -- San Francisco Artspace, July-August 1989 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0601)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Shea Stadium and CBS News (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0464)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0552)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0602)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- TV Spots, 1981, 1983, 1986, and 1989 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0556)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "The Virtues of Negative Fascination", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0677)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "The Virtues of Negative Fascination" (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0598)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- CNN -- Stanford Conference on Design, July-August 1987 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0596)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Mark Pauline -- 1989 Sculpture Grant Award Exhibition -- San Francisco Artspace, July-August 1989 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0600)
  - Art in the Anchorage 5 by Multiple Artists, 1988
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 88, Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 139, Folder 6-8)
    - Slides (Box 118, Folder Sleeves 18-25)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY (Box 146, Dvd 179.0196)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Complete Performance (Box 146, Dvd 179.0212)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- NTSC Dub (Box 146, Dvd 179.0214)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Ledge, Stage Left Cutaways (Box 148, Dvd 179.0405)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Long Shot from Front (Box 146, Dvd 179.0208)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Third Row Wide Shot (Box 145, Cd 179.0152)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Third Row Tight In (Box 148, Dvd 179.0407)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Contraband, Evol (Box 145, Cd 179.0148)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Scott Sherk, Joel Sanders, Ed Tomney, and Brigid Kennedy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0210)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Joan Jonas Soundtrack (Box 145, Cd 179.0079)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Long Shot from Front (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0207)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0195)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Complete Performance (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0211)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- NTSC Dub (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0213)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Ledge, Stage Left Cutaways (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0404)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Third Row Wide Shot (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0151)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Station House Opera -- Piranesi in NY -- Third Row Tight In (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0406)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Scott Sherk, Joel Sanders, Ed Tomney, and Brigid Kennedy (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0209)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Contraband, Evol (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0147)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Joan Jonas Soundtrack (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0078)
  - Art on the Beach 9 by Multiple Artists -- Hunter's Point, Queens, July-September 1988
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 2, Folder 89, Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 139, Folder 10-12)
    - Slides (Box 118, Folder Sleeves 13-17)
  - Posters - Art on the Beach [2 items], Undated (Box Shared Fales 081, Folder 1, Folder 7)
  - Action Mail Art and Performances by Marcos Kurtycz, October-December 1988
    - Softwars Cardpost, Do You Know Hockers, Up Tiempo, Preempting Swarm, Tercera Gracia de Via Angelina, and Artforum Bombing Action -- Original Artwork and Publicity (Box 20, Folder 16-43)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Organikwars, Organrites, One Dos Tres O!, and Clavarte (Box 149, Dvd 179.0459)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Organikwars, Organrites, One Dos Tres O!, and Clavarte (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0458)
  - Envelope Art by Marcos Kurtycz, 1988 (Flat-file-folder 1 Right, Box Shared Fales 081, Folder 4)
  - UP Tiempo!: Performing and Visual Artists of the Americas by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by El Museo del Barrio, November-December 1988
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 2, Folder 91, Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 140, Folder 1-3)
    - Slides (Box 117, Folder Sleeves 14-26)
  - The First NY International Festival of the Arts Program Book, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Artist Proposal Guidelines, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Berlin Billboard Project -- Negatives and Prints, 1988-1989 (Box 140, Folder 4-5)
  - NYPR89EKT and Softwars Cardpost Mail Art by Marcos Kurtycz, February-July 1989 (Box 20, Folder 44-57)
  - Citywide -- General Correspondence and Guidelines, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 102, Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Poets in the Bars by Multiple Artists, April-May 1989
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 103, Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 140, Folder 6-8)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeve 12)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Bob Holman Interview -- NOMMO Radio (Box 145, Cd 179.0094)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Bob Holman Interview -- NOMMO Radio (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0093)
  - Light Site-ings: Holland Tunnel Drive-In Billboard by Leni Schwendinger, April 1989
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 104-105, Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Negatives and Prints (Box 140, Folder 9-10)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 147, Dvd 179.0266)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0265)
  - Automotive Votive by The Kunst Brothers (Tom Leeser and Alison Saar), May 1989
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 106, Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 140, Folder 11-13)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeves 9-11)
  - Kissing Doesn't Kill: Greed and Indifference Do by Gran Fury, July-December 1989
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 107-108, Box 38, Folder 1, Box Shared Fales 081, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, Transparencies, and Prints (Box 140, Folder 14-15)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeve 13)
  - Art in the Anchorage 6 by Multiple Artists, June-August 1989
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 109, Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 140, Folder 16-18)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeves 1-8)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- NPR -- Christiane Vaillancourt (Box 144, Cd 179.0040)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- NPR Broadcast (Box 144, Cd 179.0048)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Jessie Jane Lewis -- "Blind Ally" (Box 146, Cd 179.0178)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- NPR -- Christine Vaillancourt (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0039)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- NPR Broadcast (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0047)
    - Audio Recording -- Original -- Jessie Jane Lewis -- "Blind Ally" (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0177)
  - Lincoln Center Out-of-Doors 1 by Multiple Artists, August 1989
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 3, Folder 110, Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Contact Sheets and Prints (Box 141, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeves 17-18)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Desire Borne" (Box 148, Dvd 179.0382)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Desire Borne" (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0381)
  - Video/Musica by Multiple Artists, November 1989
    - Correspondence, Programs, and Press (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Negatives, Contact Sheets, and Prints (Box 141, Folder 3-5)
    - Slides (Box 119, Folder Sleeves 15-16)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Part 1 (Box 144, Cd 179.0063)
    - Audio Recording -- Access Copy -- Part 2 (Box 144, Cd 179.0064)
    - Audio Recording -- Original (Box 33, Folder ID: 179.0062)
  - It Was Only Art by Karen Finley -- Press, October 1989 (Box 3, Folder 112)